[{"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c90e", "question": "What is the name of the distance around the outside of a circle?", "answer": "Circumference", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59f9ba95364247bf200fb899", "question": "Necrophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Death or dead bodies", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fecc2f4ec223966ae8f8879", "question": "Which major sports league does not let its players to wear the number 0?", "answer": "MLS", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ee8", "question": "On what planet did the bottle city of Kandor originate?", "answer": "Krypton", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339850", "question": "How many legs does the catbus have in \"My Neighbour Totoro\"?", "answer": "12", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59049aaecf93664eb1048699", "question": "Who was Joe\u2019s co-creator for the character of Superman?", "answer": "Jerry Siegel", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5990b047b72eedf883a8c710", "question": "Toxicodendron radicans, or T. radicans, is more commonly known as what?", "answer": "Poison Ivy", "category": "science"}, {"id": "596dfda99616e6c6d4eba4f7", "question": "On the hit show \"Seinfeld\" what was Kramer's first name? ", "answer": "Cosmo", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "597cdd10e347d002c297e4ec", "question": "How was the Greek city of Troy penetrated?", "answer": "Using a wooden horse", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8f9", "question": "What type of animal was selected to test out the first electric toothbrush?", "answer": "A dog", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133cad3", "question": "In computing, the term \"bit\" is an abbreviation of what?", "answer": "Binary Digit\u00a0", "category": "science"}, {"id": "596761662b59efe0e9417ea3", "question": "What country music artist was nicknamed \"Chief\" after his maternal grandfather, who was Chief of Police?", "answer": "Eric Church", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c569", "question": "How many blowholes does a southern right whale have?", "answer": "2", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe8f82901dd7bf43be5e841", "question": "Gnosiophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Knowledge", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bfff", "question": "Who is known as \"Big Mama\" in ladies pro golf?", "answer": "JoAnne Carner", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5a4a99ac61d1b4d384d5d69e", "question": "Who directed the 1998 film \"Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels\"?", "answer": "Guy Ritchie", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b1f", "question": "In the title of a 1986 song by Lionel Richie, what part of the room was he dancing on?", "answer": "The ceiling", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a060", "question": "Who directed the 1982 movie \"The Thing\"?", "answer": "John Carpenter", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd66c32a5bfecdd737e0890", "question": "What was the first martial art to use colored belts to signify rank?", "answer": "Judo", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fef659b6ce05a3942286e6f", "question": "Who was the first actress to wear pants to the Oscars?", "answer": "Barbara Streisand", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "60173abe44491cbd7c5a179b", "question": "What is the birth name of African-American abolitionist Harriet Tubman?", "answer": "Araminta Ross -- She was born into slavery.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bec8", "question": "Who was the first man to appear on the cover of Playboy Magazine?", "answer": "Peter Sellers", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b446", "question": "What year did Joseph Merrick, also known as Elephant Man, die?", "answer": "1890", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9c0", "question": "Lake Vanern is the largest lake in which country?", "answer": "Sweden", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2e0", "question": "What year did actor Arthur Stanley Jefferson die?", "answer": "1965", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ad9df26e748bb36357acde7", "question": "The Rabbit Ears Range, Castle Peak, and Mt. Massive are all in what US State", "answer": "Colorado", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5b1744b5bb2d29f81593b6fc", "question": "In the 1986 movie \"Aliens\", what was Newt's real name?", "answer": "Rebecca Jorden", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a160", "question": "When did Sid Vicious join the Sex Pistols?", "answer": "1977", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff51a0aff04d658268c9304", "question": "Which American revolutionary figure was a philosopher?", "answer": "Thomas Paine, the patriot who penned the philosophical treatise \"The Rights of Man\" and the revolutionary pamphlet \"Common Sense\"", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a90f", "question": "What major river runs through Amsterdam?", "answer": "Amstel", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb34", "question": "In the late 1990\u2019s, what candy bar used the ad slogan \"Two for me, none for you\"?", "answer": "Twix", "category": "general"}, {"id": "592eae4ff83302ff91e46487", "question": "In which 1940s Disney film would you find a rabbit named Thumper?", "answer": "Bambi", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bcf5", "question": "What's the name of the Jolly Green Giant's sidekick?", "answer": "Little Green Sprout", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5a899c1660d398dc9cf7a6a3", "question": "Who is the Greek equivalent of the Roman god Vesta?", "answer": "Hestia", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fea3625ff048f679a45ab09", "question": "Which mammal has no vocal cords?", "answer": "Giraffe", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5af25a83b63e5727cf5a4854", "question": "What are the names of the brothers in the band \"Oasis\"?", "answer": "Liam and Noel Gallagher", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6000eda09a72b906b34e3cef", "question": "What is the fattiest human organ?", "answer": "Brain", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397a0", "question": "What 1989 Billy Joel hit was included in Junior Scholastic magazine as an educational aid?", "answer": "We Didn't Start the Fire", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339020", "question": "Which US author penned the novels \"Of Mice and Men\" and \"East Of Eden\"?", "answer": "John Steinbeck", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "58f5661433a95c66dc4fe75f", "question": "Which British opera festival was started in 1934?", "answer": "Glyndebourne", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b42", "question": "What is the name of Bilbo Baggins' magical sword in \"The Hobbit\"?", "answer": "Sting", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2ec", "question": "What US state has been led by Zell Miller and Alexander Stephens?", "answer": "Georgia", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a3a", "question": "Whose novel \"Sweet Thursday\" formed the basis for the 1955 Rodgers & Hammerstein musical \"Pipe Dream\"?", "answer": "John Steinbeck", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c99", "question": "What TV show takes place in the fictional city of Rome, Wisconsin?", "answer": "Picket Fences", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba93", "question": "In a standard deck of cards, the Jack, Queen, and King all show both eyes in what suit?", "answer": "Clubs", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f02", "question": "What author created the character of Perry Mason?", "answer": "Erle Stanley Gardner", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6015f031fe83fe1f2a824c10", "question": "The total number of years the Israelites spent in captivity is?", "answer": "430 -- The Israelite spent about 430 years in Egypt.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d76", "question": "What classic novel's subtitle is \"A Novel Without a Hero\"?", "answer": "Vanity Fair", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca95", "question": "Which disease is also known as Hansen's disease?", "answer": "Leprosy", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59ca3bec44f0f6af5b066629", "question": "What Canadian professional snooker player is nicknamed \"The Grinder\"?", "answer": "Cliff Thorburn", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5cc", "question": "What is the name given to the largest number ever used in a mathematical proof?", "answer": "Graham's Number", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fede2096ce05a3942286dcb", "question": "What does Seymour have to feed his plant in \"Little Shop Of Horrors\"?", "answer": "Human blood", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6015e56efe83fe1f2a824bbe", "question": "In which country was Buddha born?", "answer": "Nepal", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339452", "question": "What were the children allergic to in the movie \"The Others\"?", "answer": "Light", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339218", "question": "What is the theme song of the TV show \"Friends\" called?", "answer": "I'll Be There for You by The Rembrandts", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339234", "question": "What movie did Ewan McGregor get in character for by shaving his head and shedding 30 pounds?", "answer": "Trainspotting", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c207", "question": "Which country were the 1908 Summer Olympic Games held in?", "answer": "United Kingdom", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fed2598ec223966ae8f8907", "question": "A \"foo fighter\", upon which the famous 1990's band is named, is a term derived from which line of professionals?", "answer": "Aircraft Pilots", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c2e5", "question": "What do fried spiders taste like?", "answer": "Nuts", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5909cb7dbb53d1af658864d8", "question": "What band released a single in 1977 entitled \"Father Christmas\"?", "answer": "The Kinks", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c59d", "question": "What word denotes the energy an object has because it is in motion?", "answer": "Kinetic", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4de", "question": "What is the largest lake in Central America?", "answer": "Lake Nicaragua", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa98", "question": "Which country is also the world's largest archipelago?", "answer": "Indonesia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "597cd907e347d002c297e4ca", "question": "On which date is Epiphany celebrated in the traditional Western calendar?", "answer": "January 6", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b240", "question": "What royal subject married Lisa Halaby?", "answer": "King Hussein of Jordan", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fffa5b473838c5c8a417f2a", "question": "Automatonophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Ventriloquist dummies", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133921d", "question": "In which movie does Hugh Grant play a London bookshop owner?", "answer": "Notting Hill", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff2148031a458464a93c457", "question": "What do you call a vegetarian who only consumes chicken and fowl but no other meats?", "answer": "Pollotarians", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ffa4394c73aa70ea0b70b17", "question": "Flanders is part of which country?", "answer": "Belgium", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fd6a2806c0f9723ab15cb42", "question": "Who was the first U.S. senator to be elected president?", "answer": "James Monroe", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c92a", "question": "What is a dromedary?", "answer": "One-humped camel", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe7ca28877e98cb97778a03", "question": "In what sea would you find the Admiralty Islands?", "answer": "Bismarck Sea", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c93e", "question": "What is a group of bears called?", "answer": "Sleuth", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a01e", "question": "What day of the week do the Bangles wish it was in \"Manic Monday\"?", "answer": "Sunday", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe77075eec85e375820b2f9", "question": "Where is the \"Top of Europe\"?", "answer": "Jungfraujoch, Switzerland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe76e25eec85e375820b2da", "question": "Which country does the island of Curacao belong to?", "answer": "The Netherlands", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4b8", "question": "\"Video Killed the Radio Star\" was the debut music video on which channel in 1981?", "answer": "MTV", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ae1c", "question": "How many battleships were sunk during the attack of Pearl Harbor?", "answer": "5", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ffa3a29c73aa70ea0b70ade", "question": "What river runs through Baghdad?", "answer": "The\u00a0Tigris River", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5989aac5cb8751d53e7d7605", "question": "Which sea, that is part of the Southern Ocean, has the alternative name \"George IV Sea\"?", "answer": "Weddell Sea", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a970", "question": "What nation's legislative body is named the Diet?", "answer": "Japan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ffb667e5dad637d903c8837", "question": "The Hunua Ranges is located where?", "answer": "New Zealand", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a1a", "question": "What female band had hits in the 1980\u2019s with the songs \"Cruel Summer\" and \"Venus\"?", "answer": "Bananarama", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc86", "question": "What color is the one-ball in a traditional billiards set?", "answer": "Yellow", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c41e", "question": "What are baby Koalas called?", "answer": "Joeys", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b713", "question": "According to tradition, what must be saved from the yule log?", "answer": "A piece of wood to light next year's yule log", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe65797ae7e414034b5aede", "question": "Facebook co-founder Sean Parker was also the co-founder of which company?", "answer": "Napster", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fc2f63fcee580c7f8fd1e5c", "question": "What was the leading cause of combatants' deaths during the American Civil War?", "answer": "Disease", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d2f", "question": "Which two actresses on TV's \"Charlie's Angels\" were meant to be portraying sisters?", "answer": "Farrah Fawcett-Majors and Cheryl Ladd", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f27", "question": "\"The Great Rock 'n' Roll Swindle\" is a mockumentary about what band?", "answer": "The Sex Pistols", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea4484ff048f679a45ab8e", "question": "What is the only canine that can climb trees?", "answer": "Gray fox", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aad6", "question": "In which continent would you find the Lena River?", "answer": "Asia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c28", "question": "Who wrote \"Little House in the Big Woods\"?", "answer": "Laura Ingalls Wilder", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ecf", "question": "Whose last book was \"Oh, the Places You'll Go\"?", "answer": "Dr. Seuss'", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6015e963fe83fe1f2a824be5", "question": "Who is Temujin better known as?", "answer": "Genghis Khan", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8aa", "question": "What country is the original home of Bacardi rum?", "answer": "Cuba", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe7d564877e98cb97778a64", "question": "What actor played the school principal in E.T., only to have his scene cut when Spielberg decided that his presence would be too distracting?", "answer": "Harrison Ford", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fdc1408469bb8041d07a083", "question": "A ganache is a combination of cream and what?", "answer": "Chocolate", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392ac", "question": "Which actress got her start at age 13 playing the 12-year old prostitute Iris in a 1976 thriller?", "answer": "Jodie Foster", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c385", "question": "In medical terminology, the \"voice box\" is known as what?", "answer": "Larynx", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6b4", "question": "What type of bird is the Brown Thrasher?", "answer": "Songbird", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ffa3d18c73aa70ea0b70af3", "question": "What is the most mountainous country in the world?", "answer": "Bhutan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339aee", "question": "What was Underdog's secret identity, which was also his occupation?", "answer": "Shoeshine boy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3e7", "question": "Which African nation gained its independence on July 9, 2011?", "answer": "South Sudan", "category": "history"}, {"id": "591c37bc815febcc896f9273", "question": "What is the tenth sign of the Zodiac?", "answer": "Capricorn", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a1e", "question": "What period preceded Picasso's \"Rose Period\"?", "answer": "Blue Period", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fde52b6c6c6b019850c9a98", "question": "In Proverbs, when Solomon refers to the lazy, he tells the sluggard to look to what insect for an example?", "answer": "Ant", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c346", "question": "What fluid was the chemical \"taurine\" first derived from?", "answer": "Ox bile", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c37f", "question": "A male duck is properly known as what?", "answer": "A drake", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ea0", "question": "What future star's neck is broken by Bruce Lee in the cave fight in \"Enter the Dragon\"?", "answer": "Jackie Chan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5ef", "question": "What is the longest river solely in England?", "answer": "The Thames", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59008cfbcf842fa4c4ba96a6", "question": "What is the capital of Poland?", "answer": "Warsaw", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e1f", "question": "For an SNL monologue, who once played the banjo with an arrow through his head?", "answer": "Steve Martin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "601b4bba49076251badbeac7", "question": "How many rooms are there in Buckingham Palace (total number)?", "answer": "775 -- It includes 19 State rooms, 92 offices, 52 Royal and guest bedrooms, 188 bedrooms for staff and 78 bathrooms.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a69c", "question": "The Canadian city of Windsor is linked to what US city by the Ambassador Bridge?", "answer": "Detroit", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58dba70f874c93a3298b2160", "question": "What is Peter Chriss\u2019 persona name in the band KISS?", "answer": "The Catman", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5aa", "question": "In which US state is Alcatraz Island located?", "answer": "California", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339499", "question": "In what city did Ann Romano raise her two daughters on the show \"One Day at a Time\"?", "answer": "Indianapolis", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f33", "question": "Which band member of Red Hot Chili Peppers died of drug overdose?", "answer": "Hillel Slovak", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a0cc", "question": "What are the names of the twins on the TV show \"Thundercats\"?", "answer": "WilyKit and WilyKat", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59bb2911c9bff04efae6d754", "question": "In what 1967 film did Gene Hackman earn his first Oscar nomination?", "answer": "Bonnie and Clyde", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f031133890c", "question": "What was the sequel to \"Little Women\"?", "answer": "Good Wives", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe9f0bdff048f679a45aaa5", "question": "Tachophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Speed", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fefc0e46ce05a3942286f0a", "question": "What is the name of the British ship in the film \"Master and Commander: Far Side of the World\"?", "answer": "H.M.S. Surprise", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6008dcfef4f3bc4a292f861d", "question": "Whose \"Civil Disobedience\" essay inspired Dr. Martin Luther King King. Jr.?", "answer": "Henry David Thoreau (Thoreau wrote it after he was imprisoned for protesting slavery by refusing to pay his poll tax.)", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b83b", "question": "How many horizontal rows of stars are there on the U.S. flag?", "answer": "9", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5feccaecec223966ae8f889c", "question": "How many pounds of food does Hollywood superstar Dwayne \"the Rock\" Johnson consume daily?", "answer": "The Rock is well known to consume 10 pounds of food daily and accordingly travels with a 40,000-pound personal gym set!", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113394d9", "question": "What is D.J.'s full name on the TV show \"Roseanne\"?", "answer": "David Jacob", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c331", "question": "What is brass an alloy of?", "answer": "Copper and zinc", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ed4", "question": "What horror movie was based on the novel \"Ratman's Notebooks\"?", "answer": "Willard", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe7c588877e98cb977789b1", "question": "What city did Frank Sinatra help immortalize as \"That Toddlin' Town\"?", "answer": "Chicago", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1c2", "question": "What fired general later ran against Lincoln in the 1864 election?", "answer": "George McClellan", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5b323204bf195a31e15d738b", "question": "Belmopan is the capital of which country?", "answer": "Belize", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58dba1a6874c93a3298b2129", "question": "What year did Jimmy Carter assume office as the 39th President of the United States?", "answer": "1977", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b0e", "question": "Who is Johnny Storm better known as in the comic book series \"Fantastic Four\"?", "answer": "Human Torch", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f9a", "question": "What book was the film \"Three Days Of The Condor\" based on?", "answer": "Six Days Of The Condor", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd89", "question": "What type of animal is the Japanese monster, Megalon?", "answer": "Beetle", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5be", "question": "Who is the inventor of Coca Cola?", "answer": "John Pemerton", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d0f", "question": "What movie's first sequel featured the subtitle \"On the Move\"?", "answer": "Mannequin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fc8421e78d18506ae1fe48a", "question": "What is the name of the tallest tree in the world?", "answer": "Hyperion", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399ba", "question": "What actor played the role of Officer Don Orville in the TV show \"Third Rock From The Sun\"?", "answer": "Wayne Knight", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339585", "question": "Which rock star was \"The Man Who Fell on Earth\"?", "answer": "David Bowie", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af53", "question": "During World War II, who was the \"Desert Fox\"?", "answer": "Field Marshall Rommell", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133afcb", "question": "Who was the first American astronaut to enter space?", "answer": "Alan B. Shepard", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58ec22f68dc25ca9e12ef62b", "question": "As whom was J\u00e1n Ludv\u00edk Hyman Binyamin Hoch better known?", "answer": "Robert Maxwell", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff6719f52a821ff76ae8b25", "question": "Which popular tea blend is named for a British Prime Minister?", "answer": "Earl Grey", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ad7ecafb24f84e0b9f9ffe9", "question": "What is a sphygmomanometer used to measure?", "answer": "Blood pressure", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339363", "question": "Where did Helen and Joel get married on the TV show \"Wings\"?", "answer": "The bathroom", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fdc15c4469bb8041d07a08c", "question": "What does \"dim sum\" mean in English?", "answer": "Touching heart", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b259", "question": "Which amendment to the US Constitution deals with the right to bear arms?", "answer": "Second", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb4a", "question": "What is the name for Germany's high-speed highways?", "answer": "Autobahn", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe7ce32877e98cb97778a3e", "question": "The famous commercial port of Sidon is located in which Arab country?", "answer": "Lebanon", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a039", "question": "What is Quagmire's daughter's name in the TV show \"Family Guy\"?", "answer": "Anna Lee", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd6670ba5bfecdd737e086a", "question": "What US state was the first to ban drivers from talking on handheld devices?", "answer": "New York", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a44c", "question": "In what country was the Terracotta Army sealed underground?", "answer": "China", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b391", "question": "Who won the first Boat Race between Oxford and Cambridge?\u00a0", "answer": "Oxford", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339cca", "question": "What kind of gem is El Corazon which is \"romanced\" in the movie \"Romancing the Stone\"?", "answer": "An emerald", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5990b013b72eedf883a8c70e", "question": "In what country do people speak the language they call Nihongo?", "answer": "Japan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf17", "question": "At which sport was Fred Perry crowned world champion in 1929?", "answer": "Table Tennis", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133986d", "question": "In Disney's \"Cinderella\", who gives her a new gown and carriage for the ball?", "answer": "Her fairy godmother", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b16", "question": "What actor did Melanie Griffith marry, and divorce, twice?", "answer": "Don Johnson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338dd3", "question": "From what language did English borrow the word \"soy\"?", "answer": "Japanese", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bf2", "question": "In which city was the composer Ludwig Van Beethoven born?", "answer": "Bonn", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b04f", "question": "What holiday was first celebrated in Spokane, Washington on June 19, 1910?", "answer": "Father's Day", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a533", "question": "The Missouri River flows into what river?", "answer": "Mississippi River", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c3a", "question": "By what name is the author Theodor Geisel better known?", "answer": "Dr. Seuss", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339245", "question": "What is the birth country of Russell Crowe?", "answer": "New Zealand", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8b6", "question": "In what city would you find Balboa Park?", "answer": "San Diego", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397f0", "question": "Which actress was jailed in 1982 for tax evasion?", "answer": "Sophia Loren", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59ae92ec574a5ce6b56b8233", "question": "What sport is played by the Chicago Bulls?", "answer": "Basketball", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba06", "question": "What sport did George Bush Sr. play at Yale University?", "answer": "Baseball", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5be57cc15415ba52ed6f0aa4", "question": "Who is the boss on NBC's TV Show \"The Office\"?", "answer": "Michael Scott", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133986b", "question": "In Disney's \"Cinderella\", how many evil Step-sisters does Cinderella have?", "answer": "2", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a40", "question": "In 2000, the Black Crowes released a live album recorded with what legendary guitar player?", "answer": "Jimmy Page", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b15c", "question": "Who was awarded the Nobel Peace Prize in 1979?", "answer": "Mother Teresa", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395ac", "question": "Julia Roberts and Hugh Grant were paired in what romantic comedy?", "answer": "Notting Hill", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe523921bf59ab7d2e380f0", "question": "In which country would you find fried meatballs served with potatoes and gravy called frikadeller?", "answer": "Denmark", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a30c", "question": "Who played the role of Marcy Runkle on the TV show \"Californication\"?", "answer": "Pamela Adlon", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396eb", "question": "On the Academy Awards statue, what is Oscar standing on?", "answer": "A reel of film", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e22", "question": "What city's orchestra did Eugene Ormandy conduct for forty-four years?", "answer": "Philadelphia's", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c21f", "question": "When was \"Macho Man\" Randy Savage born?", "answer": "1952", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396f9", "question": "What color is Spock's blood?", "answer": "Green", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f87", "question": "What actress earned an Oscar nomination for her first screen appearance in \"Dreamgirls\"?", "answer": "Jennifer Hudson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fb7", "question": "In Shakespeare's play who was the wife of Othello?", "answer": "Desdemona", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c24b", "question": "How many wings does a bee have?", "answer": "Four", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8fe", "question": "What London street is home to a famous theater and, in a children's song, to \"the Muffin Man\"?", "answer": "Drury Lane", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6018bbd2d96d05b23b28164f", "question": "What event prompted the first New Year\u2019s Eve ball drop in Times Square?", "answer": "New York Times paper owner Adolph Ochs hired a metal worker to build the ball-drop due to a fireworks ban in the city.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c28e", "question": "What are you if you are myopic?", "answer": "Near-sighted", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339cf6", "question": "In which movie did Billie Burke portray a witch?", "answer": "The Wizard of Oz", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc83", "question": "What Asian country bans the importation and sale of chewing gum?", "answer": "Singapore", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f031133893a", "question": "Who painted the Sistine Chapel ceiling?", "answer": "Michelangelo", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba56", "question": "What horse set a Kentucky Derby record in 1973?", "answer": "Secretariat", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be71", "question": "What is the Los Angeles Memorial Coliseum also known as?", "answer": "The Grand Old Lady", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339631", "question": "What city was the setting for the 1994 movie \"Miracle on 34th Street\"?", "answer": "New York City", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b5b", "question": "Which fairytale character slept for 20 years?", "answer": "Rip Van Winkle", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a49b", "question": "In what country was the concentration camp \"Treblinka\" located?", "answer": "Poland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5a9e92be7ccba3ffe45786bb", "question": "Mr. Mybug was only interested in sex with Flora in what book?", "answer": "Cold Comfort Farm", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe938d96bd93ce3a4e5f688", "question": "What branch of science is concerned with the interaction between matter and electromagnetic radiation?", "answer": "Spectroscopy", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ef8", "question": "Which literary work's title character is named Isabel Archer?", "answer": "The Portrait of a Lady", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd41", "question": "What color is New York's Staten Island Ferry?", "answer": "Orange", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5a4a955e61d1b4d384d5d679", "question": "Which fruit is affected by a grey type of fungus known commonly as Noble Rot?", "answer": "Grapes", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad64", "question": "Who coached the US basketball \"Dream Team\" to a gold medal at the 1992 Barcelona Olympic Games?", "answer": "Chuck Daly", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a51", "question": "What was the complete name of the toga party band from the movie \"Animal House\"?", "answer": "Otis Day & the Knights", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5bfdff78b668d7dfe168b5b8", "question": "In Greek mythology, who was Jason's wife?", "answer": "Medea", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe3ea4438e4e5d4832e6314", "question": "Which U.S. President started the tradition of having a national Christmas tree on the White House lawn?", "answer": "Calvin Coolidge", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5da855dd1aec824685d88d03", "question": "What is the most common street name in the United States?", "answer": "Park, according to a Washington Post study", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd2cfc92596a59cbdfbd373", "question": "Who said, \"My Best Friend is a person who will give me a book I have not read\"?", "answer": "Abraham Lincoln", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5aa", "question": "When was the Guinness beer brand first introduced?", "answer": "1759", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c841", "question": "In what organ of the human body would you find the duct of Wirsung?", "answer": "The pancreas", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ff513b4ff04d658268c92de", "question": "What naval battle between Mark Antony and Octavian is often said to mark the beginning of the Roman Empire?", "answer": "The\u00a0Battle of Actium", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fea7eb9ff048f679a45ac12", "question": "What color is Absinthe?", "answer": "Green", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a034", "question": "In the show \"Family Guy\", which US president has been seen happily singing in public about being nude?", "answer": "Bill Clinton", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aeb4", "question": "How old was General Tom Thumb when he joined P. T. Barnum's circus in 1843?", "answer": "5", "category": "history"}, {"id": "596dfa93cf3977a46e7ce447", "question": "The Statue of Liberty was a gift resulting from the diplomatic relationship between the United States and what country?", "answer": "France", "category": "history"}, {"id": "60078261bd51d85e222ab657", "question": "What artist believed he was a reincarnation of his dead brother?", "answer": "When he was five, Dali's parents told him he was a reincarnation of his older brother, who died nine months before he was born.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b962", "question": "What number shirt did Pele wear?", "answer": "10", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fef96166ce05a3942286e9a", "question": "In what Disney movie would you find the character of Briar Rose?", "answer": "\"Sleeping Beauty\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339221", "question": "Which two artists formed the band \"Wham!\"?", "answer": "George Michael and Andrew Ridgeley", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe52fb81bf59ab7d2e38117", "question": "Where is Bank of America headquartered?", "answer": "Charlotte, North Carolina", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac73", "question": "The Bronze Age was characterized by the use of which malleable metal and one of its alloys?", "answer": "Copper", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339af1", "question": "What sporting competition was the focus of the 2007 film \"Balls of Fury\"?", "answer": "Ping Pong", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c34f", "question": "What shape is the body of an Erlenmeyer flask?", "answer": "Conical", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8ca", "question": "What country did poinsettias originally come from?", "answer": "Mexico", "category": "science"}, {"id": "6018bc9ed96d05b23b281659", "question": "Ken Thompson and Dennis Ritchie co-created which operating system?", "answer": "Unix", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca45", "question": "In the human body where is your occiput?", "answer": "Back of the head", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba18", "question": "What does the abbreviation NASA stand for?", "answer": "National Aeronautics and Space Administration", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fc2f114cee580c7f8fd1e4d", "question": "Who said, \"In the end, it's not the years in your life that count. It's life in your years.\"?", "answer": "Abraham Lincoln", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5feccd3aec223966ae8f88aa", "question": "What is the name of the event where tributes are chosen for \"The Hunger Games\"?", "answer": "The Reaping", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339bb5", "question": "What actor played James Bond in two Bond films in between Roger Moore's Bond and Pierce Brosnan's?", "answer": "Timothy Dalton", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b7ea", "question": "What are the two most common coffee bean types?", "answer": "Arabica and Robusta", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe7c848877e98cb977789e1", "question": "Which country has hosted the Wife Carrying World Championships since the competition\u2019s founding in 1992?", "answer": "Finland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5bbd4c7400d154d7af00b8d1", "question": "What year did Snoop Dogg release his debut album?", "answer": "1993", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5e93a8ddd6f11f394a3b2d59", "question": "In the manga series \"Bleach\", what is the name of Toshiro Hitsugaya's zanpakuto?", "answer": "Hyorinmaru", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6015ff52fe83fe1f2a824c4d", "question": "What is the holiday related to the Nativity celebrated by some 12 days after Christmas?", "answer": "Epiphany, which is also known as Three Kings' Day or Little Christmas, is a feast day celebrated by some Christians on January 6th", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d34", "question": "Who's responsible for performing \"The Ballad of John and Yoko\"?", "answer": "The Beatles", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bf3", "question": "Which comic book hero lives in the city of Metropolis?", "answer": "Superman", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339658", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", why did Bart and Homer have to work at the carnival?", "answer": "Bart wrecked Hitler's car", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b345", "question": "In what year did Captain Cook reach New Zealand?", "answer": "1769", "category": "history"}, {"id": "592eae7df83302ff91e46489", "question": "What is a group of deer called?", "answer": "A Herd", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be3f", "question": "What is the first book of the Bible named for a woman?", "answer": "Ruth", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea4638ff048f679a45aba0", "question": "The Planting Moon is found in which month?", "answer": "May", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a32b", "question": "Which character did Eddie Murphy play in the 1982 film \"48 Hrs.\"?", "answer": "Reggie Hammond", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133998e", "question": "What was the first spin\u00ad-off series of the TV show \"The Cosby Show\"?", "answer": "A Different World", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe769eaeec85e375820b2b4", "question": "Which is the largest of the Spanish Balearic islands?", "answer": "Majorca", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a12f", "question": "At what address did the TV's \"Addams Family\" live?", "answer": "0001 Cemetery Lane", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5b323184bf195a31e15d7385", "question": "What cartoon featured a boy with a community of tiny people living in his wall?", "answer": "The Littles", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5937ec2008d98002fdd633b7", "question": "Which singer's autobiography is titled \"Take It Like a Man\"?", "answer": "Boy George's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "600781fabd51d85e222ab651", "question": "What is the title of Henri Matisse's famous portrait of his wife?", "answer": "In 1905, just prior to such works being derisively labeled as the creations of Les Fauves, he painted\u00a0\"The Green Stripe\".", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b55f", "question": "What was the first soft drink to be consumed in outer space?", "answer": "Coca-Cola", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a967", "question": "What Briton with an American wife was the governor of the Bahamas during World War II?", "answer": "King Edward VIII", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be30", "question": "How many players are there in a standard basketball team?", "answer": "Five", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b209", "question": "Which 1912 maritime disaster was responsible for numerous changes and improvements in maritime safety?", "answer": "RMS Titanic", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6018bc34d96d05b23b281654", "question": "In which country did Buddhism originate?", "answer": "Nepal", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339656", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", Marge develops a serious case of what when she gets behind the wheel of her new Canyonero?", "answer": "Road rage", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c75e", "question": "What organ gave us the word \"hysterical\"?", "answer": "The uterus", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5bbd4c1c00d154d7af00b8cf", "question": "Who recorded the 1990's song \"Baby Got Back\"?", "answer": "Sir Mix-a-Lot", "category": "entertainment"}]